So now we are going to start with the frequency, which is the RFID high frequency and the card we are
going to use or the tag we are going to use in frequency is known as Mifare Classic, And the tag which
I am going to use is Mifare classic one K memory size, right?
You can use 4k as well as EV1 tag as well.
If you are going to use Mifare classic EV1 tag, make sure its Mifare classic EV1, not ultralight EV1
because these are two different tags.
Right?
So what I'm going to use is Mifare classic one Memory cards in Mifare classic cards.
The tags have Uid of four bytes.
Right.
So these four bytes are unique as well as not changeable, right?
So any any of these tags which you are going to use like the 4k, one K or EV1, Mifare classic, all
these tags contain 4k byte uid, which is unique and not changeable.
Right?
So in the next video we are going to see how we can find this four byte Uid using Arduino and we are
going to use a module with Arduino known as RC 5 to 2.
So we are going to see all this in the coming video.